A Guide to the Virginia State Reading Association records, 1967-2010
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia State Reading Association records, 1967-2010
The Library of Virginia
44849
14.4 cu. ft. and 32 boxes
Virginia State Reading Association
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Virginia State Reading Association
Historical Information
The Virginia State Reading Association was established in 1967 and its goal is to promote literacy in Virginia through collaboration, advocacy, and professional development. It is part of the International Reading Association which was founded in 1956 to promote worldwide literacy.
Scope and Content
Records, 1967-2010, of the Virginia State Reading Association consisting of agendas, budgets, bylaws, correspondence, directories, financial records, flyers, forms, journals, lists, minutes, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, programs, questionnaires, reports, rosters, and other papers concerning the operations and objectives of the organization promoting literacy in Virginia, working as a member council of the International Reading Association.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Board of Directors, 1967-2010
Series II: Executive Board/Governing Council, 1978-2010
Series III: Leadership Workshops/Conferences, 1985-1987, 1994-1999
Series IV: Delegates Assemblies, 1980-2010
Series V: Conferences, 1970-2005
Series VI: Financial Records, 1968-2008
Series VII: Committees, 1974-2003
Series VIII: Bylaws and Policies, 1970-2009
Series IX: Correspondence, 1972-2003
Series X: Job Announcements and Positions, 1995-2004
Series XI: Directories, 1987-2009
Series XII: Local Councils
Series XIII: Awards, Honor/Merit Council, 1986-2000
Series XIV: International Reading Association, 1983-1999
Series XV: Publications, 1969-2006
Series XVI: General Subjects
Contents List
- Series I: Board of Directors, 1967-2010., Extent: 11 boxes. (Box 1-11)
  Board of Directors, 1967-2010, contains agendas, budgets, bylaws, correspondence, financial records, flyers, forms, lists, minutes, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, questionnaires, reports, rosters, and other records concerning the meetings of the board of directors. Papers include some records relating to leadership workshops/conferences. Up until 1978, the board of directors was called the executive board. In 1978, the name was changed to board of directors and a new executive board was created.
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes, 1967, January-June 1969. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee/Board meeting minutes, September 1969-May 1971. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, September 1971-April 1973. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, July 1973-April 1974. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, July 1974-April 1975. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, July 1975-April 1976. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, July 1976-April 1977. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, July 1977-May 1978. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, July 1978-May 1979. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, August 1979-April 1980. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September 1980-May 1981. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September 1981-May 1982. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, August 1982-May 1983. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September 1983-June 1984. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September 1984-June 1985. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September 1985-May 1986. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September 1986-May 1987. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September 1987-May 1988. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September 1988-May 1989. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September 1989-May 1990. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September 1990-June 1991. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September 1991-May 1992. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, September-October 1992. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 23 January 1993. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 11 March 1993. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meeting and leadership workshop, 22 May 1993. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 25 September 1993. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 20 November 1993. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 8 January 1994. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 25 February 1994. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 21 May 1994. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 17 September 1994. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 5 November 1994. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 7 January 1995. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 9 March 1995. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 20 May 1995. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 9 September 1995. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 18 November 1995. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 7 March 1996. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 18 May 1996. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 7 September 1996. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 22-23 November 1996. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 11 January 1997. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 28 February 1997. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors leadership retreat, 30-31 May 1997. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 27-28 February 1998. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 1 April 1998. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 29 May 1998. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors leadership retreat, 30-31 May 1998. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 21 August 1998. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 11 September 1998. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 6 November 1998. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 8 January 1999. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 19 February 1999. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 17 March 1999. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meeting and leadership conference, 21 & 23 May 1999. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 20 August 1999. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 10 September 1999. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 12 November 1999. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 21 January 2000. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 18-19 February 2000. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 16 March 2000. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meeting and leadership conference, 2 June 2000 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 2 June 2000 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 4 June 2000. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 18-19 August 2000. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 8 September 2000. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 3 November 2000. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 19 January 2001. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 9-10 February 2001. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 22 February 2001. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors at the International Reading Association, 1 May 2001. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 1 June 2001. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 3 June 2001. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 17-18 August 2001. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 7 September 2001. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 16 November 2001. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 4 January 2002. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 8-9 February 2002. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 6 March 2002. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 19 May 2002. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 17-19 August 2002. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 13 September 2002. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 8 November 2002. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 10 January 2003. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 7-8 February 2003. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 5 March 2003. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meeting and leadership conference, 16-18 May 2003. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 8-10 August 2003. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 12 September 2003. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 14 November 2003. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 10 January 2004. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 17 March 2004. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 21-22 May 2004. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 13-14 August 2004. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 17 September 2004. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 12 November 2004. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 7 January 2005. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 17 February 2005. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 20 May 2005. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 22 May 2005. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 12 July 2005. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 19-20 August 2005. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 16 September 2005. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 4 November 2005. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 6-8 January 2006. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 8 March 2006. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 19 May 2006. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 18-19 August 2006. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 15 September 2006. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 17 November 2006. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 19 January 2007. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 14 March 2007. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 4-6 May 2007. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 11-12 August 2007. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 14 September 2007. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 9 November 2007. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 11 January 2008. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 12 March 2008. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 19-20 April 2008. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 16-18 May 2008. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 2-3 August 2008. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 12 September 2008. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 14 November 2008. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 9-11 January 2009. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 19 February 2009. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 24-26 April 2009. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 8-9 August 2009. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 11 September 2009. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 6 November 2009. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 8 January 2010. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 10 March 2010. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 21 May 2010. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors rosters, 1970-1971, 1975-1979. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors rosters, 1979-1986. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors rosters, 1986-1989. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors miscellaneous papers, 1986-2003. (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Series II: Executive Board/Governing Council, 1978-2010., Extent: 7 boxes. (Box 11-17)
  Executive Board/Governing Council, 1978-2010, contains agendas, budgets, bylaws, correspondence, financial records, flyers, forms, lists, minutes, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, questionnaires, reports, rosters, and other records concerning the meetings of the executive board and governing council. Papers include some records relating to leadership conferences. Up until 1978, the board of directors was called the executive board. In 1978, the name was changed to board of directors and a new executive board was created. In 1997 the executive board became the governing council.
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, 29 July 1978. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, February 1980-June 1984. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, September 1984-May 1985. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, August 1985-May 1986. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, July 1986-May 1987. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, July 1987-May 1988. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, September 1988-May 1989. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, June 1989-May 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, August 1990-May 1991. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, August 1991-May 1992. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board meeting minutes, June 1992-January 1993. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board meeting, 13-14 August 1993. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board meeting, 24 September 1993. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board meeting, 19 November 1993. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board meeting, 7 January 1994. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board meeting, 24 February 1994. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board meeting, 20 May 1994. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board meeting, 5-6 August 1994. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board meeting, 16 September 1994. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board meeting, 4 November 1994. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board meeting, 6 January 1995. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board meeting, 27-28 January 1995. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board meeting, 8 March 1995. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board meeting, 19 May 1995. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board meeting, 28-29 July 1995. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board meeting, 8 September 1995. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board meeting, 17 November 1995. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board meeting, 26-27 January 1996. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board meeting, 6 March 1996. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board meeting, 29 April 1996. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board meeting, 6 September 1996. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board meeting, 4-5 October 1996. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board meeting, 10 January 1997. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board meeting, 24-25 January 1997. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board meeting, 27 February 1997. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board meeting, 30 May 1997. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Governing Council meeting, 30 May 1998. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Governing Council meeting, 12 September 1998. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Governing Council meeting, 7 November 1998. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Governing Council meeting, 9 January 1999. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Governing Council luncheon, 18 March 1999. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Governing Council meeting, 11 September 1999. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Governing Council meeting, 13 November 1999. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Governing Council meeting, 22 January 2000. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Governing Council meeting, 17 March 2000. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Governing Council leadership conference, 2-3 June 2000. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Governing Council leadership conference, 9 September 2000. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Governing Council meeting, 4 November 2000. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Governing Council meeting, 20 January 2001. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Governing Council luncheon, 23 February 2001. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Governing Council meeting, 1 June 2001. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Governing Council meeting, 8 September 2001. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Governing Council meeting, 17 November 2001. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Governing Council meeting, 5 January 2002. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Governing Council meeting, 7 March 2002. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Governing Council leadership conference, 18 May 2002. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Governing Council meeting, 13 September 2002. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Governing Council meeting, 9 November 2002. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Governing Council meeting, 11 January 2003. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Governing Council luncheon, 6 March 2003. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Governing Council meeting, 17 May 2003. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Governing Council meeting, 13 September 2003. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Governing Council meeting, 15 November 2003. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Governing Council meeting, 18-20 March 2004. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Governing Council leadership retreat, 21-22 May 2004. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Governing Council meeting, 18 September 2004. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Governing Council meeting, 13 November 2004. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Governing Council meeting, 8 January 2005. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Governing Council meeting, 18 February 2005. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Governing Council meeting, 22 May 2005. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Governing Council meeting, 17 September 2005. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Governing Council meeting, 5 November 2005. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Governing Council meeting, 7 January 2006. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Governing Council meeting, 9 March 2006. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Governing Council leadership retreat, 20 May 2006. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Governing Council meeting, 16 September 2006. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Governing Council meeting, 18 November 2006. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Governing Council meeting, 20 January 2007. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Governing Council meeting, 15 March 2007. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Governing Council leadership retreat, 5 May 2007. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Governing Council meeting, 15 September 2007. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Governing Council meeting, 10 November 2007. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Governing Council meeting, 12 January 2008. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Governing Council meeting, 13 March 2008. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Governing Council leadership retreat, 17 May 2008. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Governing Council meeting, 13 September 2008. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Governing Council meeting, 15 November 2008. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Governing Council meeting, 10 January 2009. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Governing Council meeting, 20 February 2009. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Governing Council leadership retreat, 25 April 2009. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Governing Council meeting, 12 September 2009. (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Governing Council meeting, 7 November 2009. (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Governing Council meeting, 9 January 2010. (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Governing Council meeting, 11 March 2010. (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Governing Council leadership retreat, 22 May 2010. (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Executive Board/Governing Council miscellaneous papers, 1996. (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Series III: Leadership Workshops/Conferences, 1985-1987, 1994-1999., Extent: 1 box. (Box 18)
  Leadership Workshops/Conferences, 1985-1987, 1994-1999, contains agendas, correspondence, financial records, flyers, lists, memorandums, minutes, reports, rosters, surveys, and other papers regarding the organization and operation of leadership workshops and conferences.
  - Leadership workshop, 1985-1987, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Leadership workshop, 20 May 1995. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Leadership workshop, 17-18 May 1996. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Leadership workshop, 30-31 May 1997. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Leadership conference, 29-30 May 1998. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Leadership conference, 21-22 May 1999. (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Delegates Assemblies, 1980-2010., Extent: 1 box. (Box 18)
  Delegates Assemblies, 1980-2010, consists of agendas, bylaws, correspondence, financial records, minutes, and notes concerning the annual delegates assemblies held by the VSRA.
  - Delegates Assemblies, 1980, 1982-1984. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Delegates Assemblies, 1985-1988. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Delegates Assemblies, 1989-1991. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Delegates Assembly, 1992. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Delegates Assemblies, 1993-1995. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Delegates Assembly, 1996. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Delegates Assemblies, 1997, 1999-2001. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Delegates Assemblies, 2002-2004, 2006-2007. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Delegates Assemblies, 2008-2010. (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Series V: Conferences, 1970-2005., Extent: 5 boxes. (Box 19-23)
  Conferences, 1970-2005, contains agendas, bookings, booklets, brochures, budgets, correspondence, financial records, flyers, forms, lists, minutes, programs, proposals, registration forms, rosters, schedules, and other papers concerning the booking, planning, and arranging of the conferences, as well as the conference itself.
  - Conferences, 1970-1978. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Conferences, 1980-1981, 1983-1984. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Conference, 1985. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Conference, 1986 (correspondence). (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Conference, 1986 (budget, committees--steering, hospitality). (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Conference, 1986 (registration, program, signs, displays, exhibits, hotel, evaluation forms). (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Conference, 1986 (miscellaneous papers). (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Conference, 1986 (envelopes, stationery, folders, swatches). (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Conference, 1987. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Conference, 1988. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Conference, 1989. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Conference, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Conference, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Conference, 1992. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Conference, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Conference, 1994. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Conference, 1995 (folder 1 of 3). (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Conference, 1995 (folder 2 of 3). (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Conference, 1995 (folder 3 of 3). (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Conference, 1996 (including arrangements). (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Conference, 1996 (exhibits committee--folder 1 of 3). (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Conference, 1996 (exhibits committee--folder 2 of 3). (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Conference, 1996 (exhibits committee--folder 3 of 3). (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Conference, 1996 (exhibitors list). (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Conference, 1997 (arrangements). (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Conference, 1997 (exhibits committee). (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Conference, 1998 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Conference, 1998 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Conference, 1998 (exhibitors). (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Conference, 1998 (exhibits--folder 1 of 2). (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Conference, 1998 (exhibits--folder 2 of 2). (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Conference, 1998 (exhibit space requests--folder 1 of 2). (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Conference, 1998 (exhibit space requests--folder 2 of 2). (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Conference, 1999. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Conference, 1999 (arrangements). (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Conference, 2000. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Conference, 2000 (exhibitor's package). (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Conference, 2001 (program sessions--folder 1 of 3). (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Conference, 2001 (program sessions--folder 2 of 3). (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Conference, 2001 (program sessions--folder 3 of 3). (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Conference, 2001 (financial). (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Conference, 2001 (exhibitors). (Box 22, Folder 9)